I will contact you again
-Jay
-Shh
So what you mean is...
Everything you told me before was all a lie, right?
Yeah
I found your sister's diary...
The part that was torn off
Haven’t told anyone yet…
Sister Jina was...
There is video recording in the operating room
we must find first
You can't let your father find you
Because Yeli will never miss this opportunity
It turns out you deliberately set a trap for my dad to jump.
Your dad...
to cover up one's crimes
Even his own daughter can be killed
He must have thought it was all over
If he knew there was evidence...
He will definitely take action
Yeah
I plan to follow him
i need your help
Must let him see
we are looking for your sister
Recorded video of the operating room
In this case, Dad will definitely beat us to it.
Empty the room in the exam hall
But how did your father know that Sister Jina that day...
Will go to Gangnam Station
If that video is obtained by the other party
do you know what will happen
This is something you caused. You can handle it yourself.
I've already booked a flight ticket
No
You're not allowed to go anywhere until this matter is resolved.
Are you going to lock me up too?
If you have the guts, give it a try
What did you do as a mother of your children?
Can't you go and coax her?
Our plan succeeded
My mother should go to see Liu Jiena tomorrow
to you
Yeah
where are you going
Won't you tell me?
Tell the lawyer for us
Liu Jiena will be able to testify in court tomorrow
what
I'll call you later
Hello
[3 hours before trial]
[鴴Quan]
Where is she going?
[15 minutes after the court session]
Your Honor, we request additional witnesses.
We would like to raise an objection
They did not apply in advance
This person was on the day Yu Daohe died.
The only person in the operating room who witnessed the entire process
To protect the safety of witnesses
Failure to apply in advance
please forgive me
Agree…
Additional witnesses
Let's adjourn the court for now
Dean, is there anything else I don't know?
It's okay
Jay
What's wrong
how is the situation
where are you now
Well...
Hello
-Hello
-How are you doing?
Hello everyone
Hello…
Already so big
Seulgi
I want to…
We may not be able to take Sister Jina back.
Let's take a photo together for you guys
good
Come and see here one two three
Damn it, we were fooled
Damn...
The witness didn't come
Don’t send out press releases yet.
good
Let's go
[Court]
Jay, it’s time for you to go home, right?
I'll call you later
Let's go
She even went to the kindergarten to take photos with the children
As if you wanted to show it to me on purpose
What about Jay? How did she react?
She's angrier than me
Because she couldn't find her sister
Although I don’t know whether I should say this or not
But do you believe Jay too much?
Our plan succeeded
My mother should go to see Liu Jiena tomorrow
If you hadn't misjudged
The whereabouts of Jai Yi’s mother
That means someone in the middle leaked the secret
what do you want to say
Impossible
Liu Taijun never wavered from beginning to end
It seems like he already knew
What evidence will we produce?
Even when we applied to subpoena Jina to testify
Instead, he appeases his lawyer
As if he knew we couldn't bring him
The way Jenna is coming
where are we going now
Actually I've always been curious
Why was Jina in the operating room at that time?
Because…
Jai, her father is a monster
He could just give her the topic
Why does she need to go into the operating room?
Seulgi
are you okay
Seulgi, are you okay?
Jay, you also want to know...
Are you injured? Are you okay?
The day your sister...
Why are you in the operating room?
sister
what are you doing here
let's go out
what did you do to her
The initiator…
It's your sister, not me
Dad, am I great?
Lie
Do you think the murderer is your sister?
Will I give up?
You just want to believe that I killed Teacher Yu Daohe
This way you have an excuse to resist
If Jina really puts
The situation in the operating room was recorded
I really want you to see it
That way you can clear my name
Jai, think about it carefully
To make a healthy person
How much effort does it take to "die a reasonable death"?
I've had enough of helping your sister clean up her mess.
sister
tell me
Did you kill Teacher Yu Daohe?
Say it quickly
She was in pain
So I wiped her memory
It was you who ruined my sister
you are a failed father
Stop talking about how many things you have done for Liu Jiena
you just can't accept it
I have an imperfect daughter
Isn't it?
Jay
I do this all for you
I don't want your efforts
Dragged down by your sister's scandal
Do you really not understand your father’s painstaking efforts?
How ridiculous
It turns out you also have a "heart"
don't worry
Liu Jiena and I are different
you want a perfect daughter
I will fulfill your wish
Hope you…
don't let me down
The tires are flat
It can be seen with the naked eye to this extent
strange
Tires don’t leak because they are old
what
Did you mess with someone?
Someone will deliberately puncture your tires
You say so?
[Liu Jieyi]
What's wrong
Because the tire is too old and flat
I was scolded by the master just now
Then... just change the tires?
No, I want to scrap this car.
This car is so old
Your dad said he bought the car the year you were born.
It’s almost 20 years ago
sorry
It seems like I should ask your opinion first
Don’t scrap it yet
It doesn't matter
What if another accident happens?
It's better to scrap it
Too lazy to cook
Let's have dinner out today
OK
The meeting time is over
Everyone, tighten your skin a little bit
There really isn't much time left
Let’s work hard today too
Teacher, Jay didn't come today
She's sick
I won’t come to school for a while
is she sick
What's wrong with you?
You should know better than me, right?
Aren't you best friends?
The number you dialed does not exist
Please confirm before dialing
Classmates…
Outsiders are prohibited from entering here
I'm Jay's friend
I'm here to find her
If you don't leave, I'm going to call the security guard.
what are you arguing about
sorry
Please leave quickly
please leave
Jay
Don't come here
I can't contact you
Do you know how worried I am?
why don't you come to school
are you really sick
Don't stand there, let me see your face
How on earth did you get first place in the exam if you are so stupid?
what
Don’t you understand yet?
Why do I keep you by my side
Dad
Did Liu Jiena really give up the university entrance exam?
Keep your voice down
The news has spread all over the Internet
Caihua Girls' High School ranked first in the school
The daughter of the director of J Medical Center
Escape from the college entrance exam room
Jay, go home
Where is sister now?
She needs some quiet time alone now
So I won’t be back in the short term
Teacher Yu Daohe, who is a member of the committee that proposed the question
Died on my dad's operating table
My sister is also missing
Sure enough, the key to victory or defeat this year...
Still on such a difficult topic?
Who wants to explain it?
Good Xiaojing
The math problem that my sister did the day before
It’s exactly the same as the exam question
I knew it then
When I was in Liu Jiena’s folder
when i see your name
I'm sure
It must be Teacher Yu
Secretly leaked the test questions to her
And your transfer
It is also one of the conditions of this transaction
do you know
You are like a litmus paper
To test my dad's guilt
My dad hates your existence to the extreme.
Do you know how funny it is to see him like that?
Okay, stop talking
By the way, there's something I really want to know
Do you really think I'm on your side?
Think about it
I was the one who sold you the medicine
I was the one who stole Teacher Yu’s phone
To stop you from swapping the body
I was the one who told it out
Everything was not my dad's idea
Of course
There were still some twists and turns during the process.
I was also worried that you would find out
But you quickly chose to believe me
What a risk
I had a lot of fun during this time
You...
can never beat us
So you also…
Stop looking for my sister
This is my last warning to you